https://www10.ShareCG.com/blogs/info/privacy-policy/

« User Agreement
ShareCG’s Grouping Feature Explained – Tutorial »
Privacy Policy
May 17th, 2015
by Team ShareCG
Internet Business Systems, Inc. (IBS) takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. (Our privacy applies to all our web sites: www.ShareCG.com, www.edacafe.com, www.mcadcafe.com, www.giscafe.com, www.aeccafe.com, and www.techjobscafe.com.)
What This Privacy Policy Covers
This policy covers how IBS treats personal information that IBS collects and receives. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that IBS does not own or control, or to people that IBS does not employ or manage.
Information Collection and Use
General
IBS collects personal information, including your e-mail address, when you sign up for an account on ShareCG.com.
Once you register with IBS and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
IBS automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP Address, IBS cookie information, and the page you request.
IBS uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products, services and payments, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
IBS will not monitor or disclose any private e-mail message or address information unless required by law, regulation, court order, or legitimate administrative purpose. Any personally identifiable information that you provide will only be used in order to provide you with a more customized and efficient service. You may receive program information and updates from IBS periodically, and have the right and ability to opt out of any communications not directly related to the IBS service you are utilizing.
IBS does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:
We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of IBS’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
We transfer information about you if IBS is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, IBS will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
IBS may display targeted advertisements based on personal information.
IBS does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.
IBS advertisers include companies who cater to the needs of the industry you are in. For example, in the EDA industry (www.EDACafe.com) our advertisers include primarily EDA software and hardware manufacturers.
General
You can edit your Account Information at any time by clicking here.
We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the IBS service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and IBS Newsletters that are considered part of your IBS account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.
Confidentiality and Security
We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
IBS may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your IBS account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
Questions and Suggestions
If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at:
Internet Business Systems, Inc.
Privacy Policy Issues
Phone: +1 (408)-337-6870
Category: ShareCG Site
This entry was posted
on Sunday, May 17th, 2015 at 5:00 pm.
You can follow any responses to this entry through the RSS 2.0 feed.
Both comments and pings are currently closed.
Comments are closed.
Back to 'ShareCG Blogs'
ShareCG Information
Search for:
© 2020 Internet Business Systems, Inc.
670 Aberdeen Way, Milpitas, CA 95035
+1 (408) 882-6554 — Contact UsShareCG™ is a trademark of Internet Business Systems, Inc.Report a Bug
